Let's see who dares to kick me out
Is there any of your Jiang family's seed?
This is your grandson
Would you bear to let him wander outside?
NR, stop pretending here
At your age
How could she possibly be able to conceive?
This is the hospital
How could I possibly lie to you?
Son, I'm begging you
I'm already done for
The only heir of the Jiang family
One treasury is presented
I exposed my husband's affair with the nanny
killed
In this lifetime
I will make your whole family pay for their blood debts
Xiaolan, hurry up
Come over and help me wash my feet
Zhang Guifen, don't go too far
Oh wow
My precious son said
He wanted his grandmother to personally serve him
If the service isn't good,
He didn't come out
Just stay inside
Let's see who is anxious
You little cutie
Wife
Honey, calm down
Be careful of the child in her belly
If it weren't for your own consideration,
Because our Jiang family has grown them
I already got you out
Don't get too angry
That's not right
Jiang Chengang's look
It wasn't the look he gave his daughter-in-law at all
Oh my god, Gang
Be gentle
But what about carrying your child?
Don't hold him down